{
    "id": "2af5db24174045d3912df7465320cc04",
    "title": "Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Each of the four boys …………………… clever.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after each and every.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither of them …………………… there.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after each either and neither.",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… books are lost.",
            "description": "Possessives are Group A determiners. They cannot go before Group B determiners (all, some, any, either, neither etc.)",
            "answers": [
                "My all",
                "All my",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The two brothers quarreled with ……………………….",
            "description": "Each other is used to talk about two people or things.",
            "answers": [
                "one another",
                "each other"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Your need is greater than …………………..",
            "description": "Mine means my need here. ",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "me",
                "mine"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "John and …………………… are friends.",
            "description": "Pronouns used as subjects should be in their subject form.",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Rahul and I …………………… cousins.",
            "description": "When the subject is made up of two or more singular nouns, the verb should be plural.",
            "answers": [
                "am",
                "are",
                "is"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is older than …………………… am.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me",
                "myself"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "None of us …………………….. seen him.",
            "description": "Singular verbs are more common after none.",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "My essay is better than …………………..",
            "description": "Yours means your essay.",
            "answers": [
                "your",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Every light …………………… out.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after every.",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "That boy of ……………………… has broken my window again.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "your",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}